<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>python on David Gallardo</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in python on David Gallardo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building a website to display the scraped data</title>
      <link>https://example.com/p/building-a-website-to-display-the-scraped-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/p/building-a-website-to-display-the-scraped-data/</guid>
      <description>Project Description Last time, we implemented a web scraper to extract game reviews and store them in a MongoDB collection. Although the last project was valuable on its own, it would be nice to extend it so that we can also explore the data we have collected. One solution is to create a website that allows us to make queries to the MongoDB collection and display the results.
There are a number of full-featured web frameworks available in Python (Django, Pyramid, Web2py, etc ), but as our website will be a simple one, a lightweight framework like Flask will suffice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scraping Game Reviews Websites with Scrapy and Selenium</title>
      <link>https://example.com/p/scraping-game-reviews-websites-with-scrapy-and-selenium/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/p/scraping-game-reviews-websites-with-scrapy-and-selenium/</guid>
      <description>Project Description Videogames are among my favorite hobbies. I usually buy a couple of games every month so that I always have something to play in my spare time. This means I need to spend some time every day reading games reviews and articles in order to to keep myself up to date. Sure this is a good way of taking my mind off work, but lately I am getting a bit tired of it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
